Garrett Van Kranenburg • (805) 835-5096 • garrettvk.dev@gmail.com • Templeton,

Software Development Experience

While working as a construction worker in late 2019, I was introduced to programming by researching online. I've always been curious about software but after taking classes online and creating a productivity app from scratch, I was officially hooked. Not only was it intellectually stimulating but it was the first time I found myself doing something I loved. Below is a link to my portfolio which contains live demos and code for projects that I've worked on.

HYPERLINK "https://garrettvk.github.io/portfolio/"https://garrettvk.github.io/portfolio/

Currently I have been creating web apps with html, css, javascript and react in addition to countless other technologies in the web development space. I believe this is my greatest strength but I also have experience with python, creating web scrapers, web automation and interfacing with apis. While studying in college I also gained experience writing code in Java.

Work Experience

General Construction at Greater Works Construction

7343 El Camino Real Atascadero, CA

June 2018 – Present

I have worked on projects such as: Interior and exterior painting, wall texturing, wood work such as building support beams for walls, staircase rail installation, nailing exterior trim and demolition. I have experience with power tools including: hand drills, handheld and table top saws, nail guns, air compressors, and drywall texture guns. My duties also include framing, electrical, plumbing, drywall, appliance installation and painting.

Reference: William Hauck, Manager, Phone: (805) 400-7129 Email: Greaterworks805@gmail.com

Machine Operator at Ernie Ball

San Luis Obisbo March 27th, 2017 – May 31st, 2018

During my time as a Machine Operator at Ernie Ball I was responsible for operating and maintaining CNC machines. This includes loading and checking programs, filling the machine with coolant and abiding by a routine cleaning schedule. Outside of machine operation my duties included, deburring parts, checking parts, packaging, communicating with separate departments and keeping my work area clean and organized.

Reference: Aziah Navarro, Human Resources, Ernie Ball, Phone: (805) 544-7726

Machine Operator at CNC Central

Atascadero, CA

August 2013 - March 2017

As a Machine Operator with CNC Central I programmed with Mastercam, setup machines and inspected parts. This includes experience with blueprint reading, CAD/CAM applications, DNC communications, tool length settings, deburring and inspection of precision machined parts.

> Reference: Mr. Bob Veil, General Manager of CNC Central, Phone: (805) 226-0886 7343 El Camino Real, Atascadero, CA 93422

Busser at The Loading Chute

Creston, CA

May 2013 - August 2013

While employed at the Loading Chute I ensured tables were ready to receive guests, cleaned and then reset once customers were finished. As a host I welcomed guests and kept track of open seating and server rotations. Other tasks included refilling drinks, serving bread, rolling silver wear and maintaining a clean restaurant.

Reference: Mrs. Dana Zepeda, Owner of The Loading Chute, Phone: (805) 237-1259 6350 Webster Rd, Creston, CA 93432

Education

Templeton High School, Templeton, Ca High School Diploma - June 2014 Science Cuseta College, San Luis Obisbo, CA On going education in Computer